Good morning. Something I want to address with you all is the art of listening. My last two
posts on my page are really great examples of people watching to respond. And I just want you
to know that we are in such a critical time of growth in our society. And one of the things I
think that is really impacting us is our self-centeredness and our limitations in the
ability to actually listen, comprehend, and apply. I did a video based on something that Cat Williams
had thrown out there in his interview with Shay Shay. I asked about men's point of view of what
it means for women to act like men. I specifically said, I would like to hear from men. What is your
point of view on what it means for women to act like men? The amount of women that were in the
comments writing dissertations. I didn't ask y'all. I didn't ask y'all. I didn't ask y'all. And honestly,
that's very much acting like men. Inserting yourself into spaces where you were not asked.
Stop doing that shit. Stop. There was a very specific reason why I was asking men specifically
and why the space needed to be adherent to them and not to us inserting our opinions,
because that is not how you create a safe space. You still have time to go and erase your dissertation.
Second, I posted our beloved Mansour, Gaza News Live, who is live from Gaza. And he was talking about
how, you know, in Islam, there is love for all and that that's how it used to be in Palestine and that
that's not how it is now. And that this fight is not about religion, even though the Zionists are trying
to make it about that. But really, it's about people being able to be free. And the amount of people that
are like, he's talking about Islamic rule. You're listening with your Western ears. You're also so
inexperienced with listening to people who don't speak English as their mother tongue that you cannot
put it together. They're speaking broken English. And when someone is speaking a broken language,
you have to piece it together, understanding context. And that's not always easy, but it's
also something you have to know that you are either skilled or not skilled to do. So I just wanted to
bring this to y'all's attention. Because the shit that I post sometimes has complexities to it.
And sometimes the instructions are actually very simple. And the more that we can listen
and the more that we can understand and respect spaces, the better we will do at advancing and
expanding our perspectives in order to improve this space that we're in.